John, great to have you back on.
>> Great to be back. Thanks for the
invitation.
>> Of course, you're everywhere. I see you
everywhere.
>> It's crazy.
>> And people are loving you on MC
apparently because I see you every day.
You're getting Manx. People are asking
you questions. You're actually getting
back to
>> all the time. Oh, yeah. And you know, I
looked at the Man the other day. I'm
like, why am I not in the super
heavyweight yet? [laughter]
>> You're close to super heavyweight. No.
Are you almost there? Yeah,
>> I think I am.
>> Cuz you're first place in a heavyweight
right now. So, we have the heavyweight
champion in the house right now. So, I I
got a lot of things I want to talk to
you about. I, you know, especially with
recent stories with
>> SPLC that you saw that story broke. I'm
curious to know what you think about
that. The FISA thing, which is like,
hey,
>> oh yeah,
>> Nixon Carter, we thought we're going to
get away, but now we're kind of like,
well, let's keep it. I want to know why
you think we're doing that,
>> what the motives are. I have my own
ideas of why I think we're doing it. I
want to know what you think about it.
>> And then, uh, you said something about
the vault, which was like, what is this
vault, what was it called? Vault 17 or
Vault 7.
>> Vault 7. I want to hear about Vault 7.
And uh a few other things with the
scientists. You saw the whole scientist
where
>> some of them are disappearing
disappearing suicide you know or you
know missing or who knows like you can't
find these guys. Four of them being from
NASA
>> and then JPL. The other four were from
nuclear fusion and weapon. And then
three are apparently high clearance
security. Not really a direct contact.
One of them recently David Wilcox who
said he wasn't going to commit suicide
in 2022 in a tweet. apparently just
took his own life, which is pretty wild.
But I want to get into one thing right
off the bat.
>> You were on a podcast and my phone
started blowing up [laughter]
>> and I'm like, why is everybody texting
me this? Look what John said about you.
>> I said, John is about to get on the
podcast. So Rob, if you have the clip, I
want to start off with this. I want to
address it one by one by one. I want you
to cover this for me. So you're on a
podcast. I don't know which podcast this
is, but whatever it is, I was texted by
everybody with this. So go ahead and
play this clip.
>> I was watching Patrick Bet David
yesterday and Patrick is a
a hardcore Zionist. He's Iranian. I
don't think he's Jewish. I think he's
like half Assyrian and half Armenian.
>> But he's a hardcore Zionist. And not
just a Zionist, he is a like 1,000%
backer of Raza Palavi to return to Iran
and to assume the peacock throne and
blah blah blah. M
>> um and he was saying yesterday that it's
not 60%
of the Iranian people who support the
overthrow of the regime. It is 94%.
>> I don't know when I've ever said that,
but okay, let's keep going.
>> There are no polls.
>> There are no polls. You just make this
up
>> to put your your stoogge in.
>> The monarchists are crazy online. I
mean, I I saw some they've been passing
along the message that Iran only became
um Muslim 100 years ago.
>> No, that was a thousand years ago.
>> A thousand years ago. Yes. And I get
that there are still Zoroastrians and I
get all that which is the funniest part.
>> Elliot Covert Patrick Bet David is
Jewish. Okay, I stand corrected. I
wasn't sure.
>> Are you Jewish?
>> No, I'm not Jewish.
>> But I know he's not ethnic Persian. He's
>> What else is there? Is there anything
else that goes on or
>> Yeah. 94% of his friends.
>> Curious to know because I want to get
all of it out. I'm a big fan of that.
Literally, I've been asking online like
from these, you know, these Persian
monarchists.
>> See, this is
everybody wants the the Sha back. I find
that very hard to believe. Um
considering how brutal the Sha was and
the fact that he was overthrown by his
own people, right? I mean, it wasn't
like he was couped out by any foreign uh
power. Quite the o quite to the
contrary. So he um but yeah they they
literally these these Persian
monarchists they just they do polls of
like anything else. Okay, you can pause
it right there. Walk me through this.
>> No, but tell me this. It's not I'm not I
I don't want an apology. I I enjoy
talking to you. Last time we spoke uh I
think out of the seven clips that we
posted, three of them was upset Jews
because it was comments you made that
were bad against Msada and we play I
thought it was very revealing. I thought
it was great. But walk me through each
of these. Number one, hardcore Zionist,
100% backer, a Palabian, and then 94%.
Tell me.
>> Okay. The reason I said that is because
of Netanyahu's appearance. Number one.
Yep.
>> Um and uh and the comments that you made
about Palvi, like why hasn't this guy
called me back? I want him on the show.
Like why? He's irrelevant. He's a clown.
>> Why hasn't he called me back? I had him
on the show two times. Yeah, but he when
you first invited me,
>> do you know why? Do you know what
happened there? He's asking for help. He
because the interviewer, the Iranian
interviewer that interviewed me is
asking me, "Are you are you going to
help him? Are you going to help Rosa
Palvi the and we're speaking in Farsy in
English?" And I said, "No." He asked me
for help. I never heard back from him,
but I made some very bad remarks about
the guy. Have you heard what I've said
about them?
>> No. I'd love
>> I don't know how you you must not know
how monarchists think of me right now.
>> No, I think
>> Do you know they can't stand you today?
>> Good.
>> Do No, no, it's not good. I liked his
father. I don't think he's a strong
leader. He's not.
>> He was following me. His wife was
following me. His daughter was following
me. Everybody unfollowed. The monarchist
attacked me because I called Oh, it it
is in shambles with me and that
relationship. Rob, maybe play a clip
>> of what I said on the podcast if you
want to play that.
>> That's a badge of honor.
>> We're going to leave Iran and go. By the
way, you know what's the biggest thing
that Iranian people are saying? Hey,
Resal, why don't you go to Azar Bayan
and and say a few words from there. Come
closer to Iran. Show some stuff. He's
not doing it. The one thing about Trump,
let me tell you what was very crystal
clear about Trump, about MLE, about
Boulli. You know what it was?
>> They're willing to do the leg work.
They're willing to go out there. They're
willing to pay the price. They're
willing to drive. They're willing to
work their tails off. It's very obvious.
We, the market, said, "Who is this crazy
Elvis looking guy from Argentina? There
is no way he'll ever win making out with
people on stage. Guess what? He won. Who
is this guy that's in his early mid30s?
And by the way, let me give you what's
going to be confusing. I have a painting
of his dad in my house.
>> So, I'm a fan of his father.
>> So, this is this is not like a bash
towards
>> the family. No, of course.
>> And so, but this is towards I was
critical of him because for 47 years
he's been talking about he wants to have
Iran be free
>> and he didn't do it. And keep in mind, a
part of me is, yeah, that's the painting
in my house. That's a 15oot painting.
His father's right in the middle. My
criticism is of him.
>> But I was watching you. I'm like, why?
Did somebody tell you I'm a Zionist? Did
you Who's that?
>> It was in the It was in the chat. I was
reading the chat.
>> Did any other influencers that you go
and do interviews with? Did anybody
whisper to you off camera, "Hey, be
careful with Patrick. He's a Zionist."
>> Yes.
>> Who was that?
>> Oh, I I don't want to out him like that,
but he said, "Oh, you're going on PBD."
I said, "Yeah." He said, "Be careful.
Patrick comes out swinging on Israel."
>> Is this a big name?
>> Yeah, it's a pretty big name.
>> One of the biggest names. [laughter] So
then I know who it is.
>> I don't want to I don't want to.
>> Was his family in the CIA before? Maybe.
>> I I I've got to stop.
>> Okay. All right.
>> But but but I want to apologize on the
record because I was wrong.
>> Okay. So So that and and the and the uh
the BB side because you know who's the
only person in the world that
interviewed BB and Nick Fuentes within
30 days?
>> It's got to be you.
>> It's only me.
>> It's got to be. So, you know what the
problem is with me, John? This is the
problem. The same people that want
freedom of speech, that pitch it
>> Yeah.
>> don't practice it.
>> What do I mean by that? They generally
want to only talk to people that agree
with them.
>> Yes.
>> You and I don't agree on maybe a few
things.
>> No. Which is why I love the
conversation. I love the conversation
because
>> my my thoughts are Alicia, just bring it
to me. It's totally fine. My thoughts
are it's like, man, I I don't know. He
He's a CIA guy. He must know more than I
do. He has some experience. I want to
know. But
>> I'm wrong and I apologize.
>> No, let's go to the other one because I
want to clear all of this up. Let's go
to the one about when you said 94%. I'd
love to know when I said 94%. Rob, can
you take one of the language learning
models? Matter of fact, why don't we do
both of them? Take uh take Chachi BT and
do Grock and ask a question. How do you
want to pose this question? What
percentage of Iranians don't support the
IRGC?
What percentage of Iranians don't
support the IRGC?
Okay. Ask the same exact question. So,
what we'll typically do is we'll ask
different and we'll go do our own and
then we'll look at the numbers that's
being given. Okay.
>> Wow.
>> This is which one? What does it say? Uh
around 80 to 92% of Iranians appear to
not support the IRGC
>> based on available polls supportly like
the direct polling on the IRGC challenge
and due to Iran repression,
surveillance, and self-censorship. Okay,
great. leaked internal Iranian
government poll 2025 commissioned by the
presidency a confidential report found
92% of Iranians hate the regime and
that's from Yahoo explicitly including
Supreme Leader Kame and the IRGC not
just specific officials or policies this
was cited by Iranian experts and aligns
with widespread dissatisfaction
gam is the one that I saw by the way I
haven't even seen the one above that
we're reading for the go to the gamut
one gammon says what independent parts
online poll 10,000 13 to 14 have
confidence in the IRGC so that leaves
another 86 and what does it say broader
uh regime rejection only about 15 to 20%
want Islamic Republic to continue 70 to
80% favor regime change or major
transformation high agreement 70% with
designating the IRGC as a terrorist
organization in Iran can you go to the
is this uh Chad GBT or Gro
>> that was Gro
>> okay let's see what Chad GBT says zoom
in a little bit
>> okay so direct IRGC spent 2019 19
Maryland poll 80%
uh Maryland Iran puka that's Maryland so
you can criticize that because that's
from here 80%.
>> Gam is the same one I think Gam is from
Netherlands 71% of Iranians oppose
>> 20% support. So you see what numbers
we're repeating we're repeating reports
that are coming in. So it's not a
>> you're you're right and I'm wrong and I
apologize.
>> No I I appreciate that. And the and the
last one I want to show you, which is
crazy to get this out of the way so we
can have our uh uh uh conversation, is
do you know who I brought on the podcast
who never agreed to go on the podcast
with anybody? And when he came in, he
was the most suspicious guy here looking
at me saying, "Why do you have me on the
podcast?" You know who it was?
>> No. Who's that?
>> The co-founder of IRGC.
>> No.
>> That guy right there. Mosen Sazada.
Okay. Do you know who he was?
>> How did I miss that? So check this out.
I'm going I'm going to show this for
you. So if you go a little bit lower to
see who is he's the founder of Go a
little bit lower. Put IRGC arrest blah
blah blah blah blah. Can we find the
IRGC there with him and Kumeni? Uh okay.
Right there in the middle.
>> There he is.
>> An Iranian journalist and political. He
was the founder of the Islamic
Revolutionary Guard
Corps after the Iranian revolution. He
was the guy. It was between him and
Kumeni that started the IRGC.
>> My god.
>> He would do the intro to all the tapes
>> where they would send in for Iranians to
listen before the revolution happened to
pin PA's people against him. This was
the voice. Then you hit Kumeni. I had
him on the podcast and the claim was
that Savak killed 100,000 people. Now
keep in mind he's the propaganda guy.
>> Sure.
>> That's at Savak which is you know
intelligence
>> Pal CIA Palab Msad. Right.
>> Right. At the end of the podcast, I
wanted to ask him, it's been 40some
years now. You were involved. Was it a
lie that Shaw killed 100,000 people?
This is not a fan of me, right?
>> This is not a a fan of the Pali. He did
not come in knowing what we were going
to talk about. Look at his answer here.
Go ahead, Rob.
>> Compare Shah with
Let me say my judgment now that many
documents have come out. uh you know for
instance on those days opposition
claimed that 100,000
political prisoners shas
there are 100,000 political prisoners in
Iran that was false
>> it was only 3,000 3500
>> 3,00
few hundred
>> right
>> um
definitely I already said first of all
his personality Sha was a better guy
than Humeni first. Second,
uh
his what he did for Iran because that he
believed in you know modernization of
Iran
was definitely better than Islamic
Republic. As I said,
>> you can pause. I would suggest if you
want to watch it, watch it. It's
fascinating because it's a little back.
I'll text it to you. I think you'll
enjoy it. But these are my positions. My
concern is John, people that have had
good relationships, there's this one guy
that I think he's the head of the snake
that behind closed doors is creating
division and creating rumors and stories
about and he's a very influential guy.
Could be the same guy that told you
stuff about me. Very heavyweight guy.
Very, very heavyweight guy. I think
we're talking about the same person. If
I tell you I've heard 10 people that he
said stuff about me behind closed doors,
that's a small number. Wow.
>> So, this keeps coming back to me. I'm
like, what is his issue? What is his
challenge? We won't talk about the name
because I don't want you to be in an
uncomfortable position. I'm not going to
push that topic. All I'm saying is I
wanted to make sure I presented this to
you. And any push back you have, please
go for it. I'm all ears.
>> No, no. I owe you an apology. As I said,
you've you've shown me wrong, and I I'm
sorry that I uh
>> perpetuated an untruth.
>> And by the way, I don't even know what a
Zionist is. What does a Zionist mean
nowadays? What is it? Like, it's like an
N-word. Like people, god forbid, they
say, "What would you say a Zionist?"
>> I think that the definition of Zionism
has has changed now. I think it's much
more
>> it's much more well, depending on your
point of political uh view, more
reactionary or more um more radical uh
than it was when it originated in the UK
in the late 19th century. Now it is now
it is
it is political Judaism strictly for
political purposes not for religious
purposes.
>> Um at the cost of everything else.
>> I I had lunch yesterday with um with um
Mother Agapia who was on the Tucker
Carlson show a couple of months back.
She's a she's a Greek Orthodox. actually
she's she's Greek Orthodox but she's in
the Russ Russian Orthodox uh uh arch
dascese of Jerusalem and um and we
talked about this and she said in the 25
or so years that she's lived in Israel
that it's changed dramatically
and she said it's changed dramatically
because of politics. The religion hasn't
changed in thousands of years. It's the
politics that have changed and have made
it so difficult. She asked me when was
the last time I was in um Israel. I said
uh 2022 was the last time I went.
>> Just a few years ago.
>> Yeah, a few years ago. I was actually
afraid I wouldn't be able to get in, but
I didn't have any problems at all. Had a
wonderful time. Um was appalled at some
of the the um
oh some of the social situations I saw
in the West Bank. I've never been to
Gaza. I've never seen it with my own
eyes. Didn't have a desire to go, you
know, on my own. And um and it's
dramatically worse just since 2022.
>> Dramatically worse since
>> for Palestinians. Yeah.
>> Okay. Got it. Yeah.
>> In in the West Bank. I mean in Gaza
obviously there's a war going on, right?
>> But I'm talking about in the West Bank.
>> Yeah. Your experience when you went
there?
>> I have to say I loved every minute of
it.
>> So your experience was a good
experience.
>> Yeah. So you think you think the
criticism because it's becoming such a
nasty like it's almost I talk to people
and some people are like I don't even go
on Twitter anymore.
>> I actually dropped I mean I have a guy
that runs my Twitter but I I don't go on
Twitter now.
>> Yeah. Because it's almost like each of
the social media accounts they have
their own nasty bots that you attack and
you know it's part of the game. You
can't have an opinion not expect people
to push back. The moment you say, "I
believe LeBron James is the worst GOAT
of all time," you're going to have
people that are going to debate the
moment you have an opinion on that. But
I think I'm right. I think he's the
worst uh uh greatest athlete of all time
because he whines so much and he
so much. And go ahead and talk about it.
Watch the comment section. Right? So, so
we can't be like, "Oh my god, don't call
me out. It's unfair. I feel bad." I
don't think that's the problem. We
deserve to be called out. Like, we
deserve to like what we just did right
now. Hey, you said it. Great. I
addressed it. I apologize. Great. we
move on and we can have our own
conversations together. I just think
it's creating division. I just think
it's creating a level of divisiveness.
Do do you think a part of it is that
guys are afraid of others getting paid?
Like do would you trust people that are
getting paid from a government you don't
trust? So let's just say some
influencers are getting paid from Apac
or Israel, some influencers are getting
paid from Russia, some influencers are
getting paid from Qatar, some influenc
are getting paid. You think that's what
the fear is where the market believes
that people are paid mouthpieces that
you don't trust them?
>> I think that's probably a part of it.
But I think that the other part and a
very powerful part is is professional
jealousy.
Yeah. I think I I feel very strongly
that a lot of this is professional
jealousy. I I hear it about you. I hear
it about Tucker. I hear it about Shawn
Ryan. People are jealous. They're
jealous of people's success. And you
know what easier thing to do than to
just go on Twitter and start yelling
about somebody?
>> Yeah.
>> There there's a there's an influencer
I'm not even going to say her name
because she doesn't deserve for her name
to be said. Uh who just out of the clear
blue sky attacked me viciously a couple
of weekends ago. I was never important
enough to attack and I've never met this
woman and just came out and attacked
>> and
>> heavyweight or middleweight.
heavyweight.
>> So, it's a heavyweight. Okay, got it.
Yeah.
>> And uh I uh I'm a communist.
Nobody in my I'm decidedly capitalist,
first of all. Nobody's ever in my life
called me a communist. And I actually
had to chuckle out loud when I read it
that I'm a communist. I'm a spy for the
Russians. No, I have a TV show that uh
that is produced by a company in Miami
and RT International happens to license
it. So, they run it. Other platforms run
it. All of a sudden, I'm a Russian spy.
Like, oh, you figured that out all by
yourself, huh? Oh, he's got a TV show
that runs once a week on this Russian
network. He must be a Russian spy and a
communist. Like, news flash. Have you
ever been to a history class? There are
no communists running Russia anymore.
Not for a very long time, but you know,
just rolled out of bed. I say this all
the time, and my friends hate when I say
it because it's mean-spirited, but any
slob can roll out of bed, log on to
YouTube or Twitter, and criticize. That
doesn't mean we have to respond to them.
>> Yeah. It's going to be non-stop. It is
It is not going to be That's not going
to slow down anytime soon. And And I
wonder like what words
no longer carry weight. I don't know if
being called a communist carries the
weight of the 80s.
>> Now, I don't think that exactly.
>> I don't think that does.
>> In the 80s that might that might have
stung a little bit.
>> Yeah. I I like bigot today. Does bigot
does bigot have the meaning today of the
'9s? I don't think so.
>> Do you remember this this little mini
trend on uh on Facebook when co when co
first started? uh admit to to um uh
prejudice.
>> Mhm.
>> And I thought, okay, I'm going to I'm
going to do this. So, I go on Facebook
and I said, I admit I am prejudiced
against Amish people. I am I grew up
with the Amish. I don't like them.
They're mean, mean-spirited. They talk
about [laughter]
>> They talk about
>> You posted this on Facebook.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And people jumped all over
me. I'm like, "People, I'm joking. It's
a joke. What's wrong with you? People
need to lighten up.
>> Yeah.
>> But this this this this is the current
situation we find ourselves in.
>> We are we are it's a and I and I hope uh
I don't know if with the So I do think
we're going to get to a point where you
know you know how today Las Vegas I
don't know if you've been to Vegas. I'm
sure you travel all the time.
>> Vegas isn't what it used to be 20 years
ago.
>> Not a chance.
>> You go to Vegas it's like it's a
freaking ghost town. Like it used to be
packed.
>> Yes it did. You know, and then you see
the stats where they're saying, "Why is
Vegas having a hard time today?" And and
you'll see numbers where they're saying
Vegas having a hard time because they're
no longer kids are no longer drinking
alcohol like they used to.
>> Uh going and hooking up today, I don't
need to go to Vegas. There's Tinder.
>> So everything Vegas offered,
>> I now have access locally and I'm no
longer interested in drinking alcohol
like a lot of, you know, maybe I did
back in the days. And so to me, I think
we're going to come to a point where
people are going to go on social media
diets. I really believe that. I think I
think people going to go on phone diets.
I think people are going to be like,
"Dude,
>> I am setting this guy aside. I'll come
in to get my information that I need,
>> but I'm not going through it the way I
was addicted. Just what do they call it?
Is it death scrolling or doom scrolling?
>> Doom scroll.
>> Doom scrolling. Just kind of going
through it. Man, that can really
>> That probably has some effects on people
today."
>> I think probably you know what I I'll
admit another thing. I doom scroll at
night. But you know, funny thing, the
algorithm is relatively quick about
determining what interests you. I have
never seen one of my own shorts. Never.
Not one. What I watch all freaking night
long as I'm laying in [laughter] bed is
people filming in public.
>> Yeah.
>> Like taking pictures of people's license
plates. And then the people who are in
the cars lose their minds and get out
and then they have to get pepper-sprayed
and then the cops come.
>> I love that stuff
>> because it's all about the First
Amendment,
>> right? But I've never seen my own
shorts.
>> Well, I've seen a lot of your shorts.
One thing One thing I do is I I watch
this this uh Jamaican pastor. I've
probably seen him preach couple hundred
times. Rob, have you seen that clip or
No.
>> No.
>> Well, you know, I don't know if I'm
going to find it or not. This guy just
this this guy fires me up. He's so
funny. But anyways, it just tells you
the the appetite and what things we're
interested in. Okay, so let's let's go
into issues. Um, Iran uh uh war US I
think you were the first one that said 3
days before the attack that it was going
to happen. I think you said it on the
19th. Was it March 19th?
>> And Marcus like what's he do you have
that clip?
>> I took a lot of for that, too.
>> Well, you did, but you ended up being
right when you announced it. You said,
hey, here's what I think is going on. XI
agent reveals US could attack Iran as
early as Monday.
>> And you said that on the 19th 20th. I
don't know the exact dates. And Rob, if
you have the video, I wouldn't mind
showing it because to to give him credit
that he was the first guy that announced
it and it happened. And so, how did you
know where did the information come
from? The truth is I've got a friend at
the White House. I have friends at the
Pentagon, friends at the CIA, friends at
the FBI.
And and this was the criticism, too,
Patrick. A a guy a guy posted a comment
like, "Oh, we're supposed to believe
that that people just walk out of the
White House and walk up to this criminal
and tell him classified defense
secrets." And I'm like, "Yeah, that's
exactly what you should believe because
that's what happened." So, I've got
friends all over Washington. I've been
in Washington for 44 years, right? We're
all neighbors and we hang out together.
I'm the only person in my church who's
not a retired colonel or lieutenant
colonel in the military. Seriously, it's
like a VFW meeting at church every
Sunday. [laughter]
And uh and so yeah, a friend of mine
said, "Hey, listen. Uh there's some
going on at the White House." I said,
"Yeah, what are you hearing?" He said,
"We really are going to attack Iran."
>> Is this a CIA guy or no? Is this a
>> He's a I should probably protect his
>> just if it's military or intelligence.
>> Military.
>> Milary. Okay.
>> Military. and he said, "We're probably
going to be attacking on Monday."
>> And I said, "Well, wait a minute. Wait a
minute." I said, "I I've been really
hedging my my language here." And what
I've been saying, this is what I told
him. What I've been saying is one of the
very first lessons that I learned at the
CIA is that if you want to determine
American military intentions, watch
naval movements. You know, we can fly
troops out all over the place. It
doesn't make any difference. If you're
going to send an an entire aircraft
carrier strike group, you mean business.
if you're gonna send two of them, you're
going to war. And we sent two.
>> And that was the determination I made.
>> Interesting. So, that was given to you.
You and Is this it Rob?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Go forward.
>> I have a friend uh former CIA officer
who was at the White House this morning
talking to his friends and he says that
a decision has been made to attack Iran
on Monday or Tuesday. The president
yesterday gave the Iranians 10 days to
uh to, you know, accept our proposals
for an end to their ballistic missile
program, an end to to uh their uranium
enrichment program and
>> it's pretty wild. See, so let me ask you
when when normally because you're in a
community and people talk, right? Like
I'm in the financial industry. I was no
longer uh sold my company almost four
years ago. For sure. So when that
happens because there's two different
ways of leaking information. The one
information is leaking where it's like
>> talk about it. Drop it. One information
is John please don't say this to anybody
else.
>> Right.
>> Which one was this?
>> I think this was please don't say this
to anybody else. To him
>> to him
>> because this was real military planning.
He panicked and said something to me.
But you're exactly right. There are two
different kinds of leagues. First of
all, the White House and the Pentagon
leak like a civ,
>> but usually those leaks are authorized
leaks.
>> Let's get an idea what public opinion is
going to be.
>> That's right.
>> Let's just see what the networks say if
we do X.
>> That's not what
>> that's been happening for decades. This
is just don't tell anybody. And you
ended up
>> you ended up sharing it and then ended
up being right. So the guy and this
isn't Joe Kent that you were talking
about.
>> Oh, no. No. You and Joe don't have you
and Joe don't have a relationship. That
would be an interesting podcast of the
two of you guests.
>> I would enjoy that very much because you
know what what I did as soon as he went
public I I called a producer that I know
and I said any chance you have Joe
Kent's contact information because I'm a
member of this group called Veteran
Intelligence Professionals for Sanity
VIPs and we wanted to give him our it's
called the Sam Adams Award for Integrity
and Intelligence. And so she sent me his
uh his info and we gave him the award.
>> Beautiful.
>> But I've never spoken to the man. So
what do you what do you think where we
are now? So if if you if that was then
that this is happening, is there any
talks today of this coming to an end?
Because there was supposed to be a
ceasefire. All right, let's do
ceasefire. Ah, I don't know if both
sides committed to the full ceasefire,
but let's just say it was a seizish fire
that they did yesterday. Yesterday at
4:45 in the morning, our time, Iran
attacks three ships. They seize two of
them. One is
>> from Panama. I think one of them's from
Greek Greece if I'm not mistaken. It is.
>> So they take that and so they and then
President Trump is like the ceasefire is
continuing indefinitely. What does that
really mean? The negotiations are going
back and forth. Where do you think we
are today?
>> I think the situation is unique because
Donald Trump is president. Donald Trump
has this innate ability to spin things
better than any previous president. I
believe I could actually see Donald
Trump saying in a nationally televised
announcement, "We won. It's all over.
We're coming home." I could see that
happening. I'm not saying it's going to
happen tomorrow, but I could see it
ending that way. Now, with that said, I
think that
this is one of those times where we need
to let the diplomats do what they're
trained to do. We have not made great
use of the Omanis. We've not made great
use of the guties or the Algerians. I
mean, these are all countries that we
work with work through over the course
of decades to carry out diplomatic
communications with Iran. I think the
bottom line is
we have one idea of what we want from
Iran, but the Israelis have a different
idea. You notice, for example, uh the
president announces a ceasefire in
Lebanon and boom, 24 hours later, the
Israelis bomb. It's because we have
competing interests. You know, there's
this old saying in Washington, there's
no such thing as permanent friends, just
permanent interests. Well, our interests
diverge with those of the Israelis on on
some of these issues, specifically Iran
and Lebanon. So I think really Patrick
the bottom line is at the end of this
we're going to end up with something
that looks very much like the JCPOA
and we're just going to say up we won
it's all over we have this agreement
pieces at hand. I think the real
sticking point is going to be what to do
with the uranium that's already been
enriched. Even if it's only 60% or 80%
or whatever it is it happens to be. Um
the American position is that they have
to give it to us. The old position was
they could transfer it to China, the
United Arab Emirates, Saudi Arabia.
We've changed our position on that. It
has to come to us. They won't send it to
us. That's going to be a sticking point.
But otherwise, you know what? I think
that I think that this conflict has also
um brought to light some American
weaknesses.
And I think the most important one is
that the conflict has pushed the
Iranians deeper into the embrace of
China, Russia and India. All three of
them, all four of them are BRICS
countries. We also know that there are
rumblings of a unified uh BRICS
currency. It's probably 30 years down
the road, but it's going to happen one
of these days. I think this conflict is
going to make it happen a little bit
more quickly and that's going to further
weaken the United States. So if if for
example the international community
either drops the petro dollar or begins
trading buying oil in yuan we're
screwed. It's going to have a long-term
dilitterious effect on the American
economy. And I think that this conflict
pushed things in that direction.
>> Yeah. And behind closed doors, China
apparently got caught sending a ship.
>> Yeah.
>> Where the president said they send him a
gift. What's in the gift? Well, it's
secret. I can't tell you what's in the
gift, but it was what? Chemical
>> missile uh uh uh weapons, you know, kind
of helping them out to have some
missiles to defend themselves.
>> That's right.
>> So, you know, we've always known they've
been close because when when uh China
signed that 25-year deal with uh Iran, I
don't know what the number was, $400
billion, $300 billion. It was a big
number. We've always seen them being
close and Iran being close to Russia
because Iran would sell
>> Sure.
>> their uh is it Shaveid uh uh uh drones,
the drones that they make,
>> the drone, they pump those drones out
like nobody
>> 20,000 a pop.
>> So, it kind of reminds you of what
happened with Ukraine and Russia where
Ukraine was attacking with their small
drones and they're the best producers of
drones.
>> So, you see similarities there, but the
difference is Ukraine was protected by
NATO.
>> Right.
>> Right. So, and US cuz it was under
Biden. So they got so much money and
funding. So Russia had to kind of sit
there and say, "What are we going to do
here?"
>> That's why everybody's so shocked at
revelations that the Russians and the
Chinese are giving the Iranians
targeting information. Of course they're
giving them targeting information.
>> Not shocked.
>> We give the Ukrainians targeting
information. Right.
>> This is We The Russians did this to us
in Vietnam.
>> Yeah. But the difference is what you
said is very important. You said the
difference is the Trump effect, right?
He knows how to negotiate. If there's
anything we've learned from 2016 to
2026,
uh, in choosing presidents, if you ask
somebody a question in 2000, what
qualities do you want in a president?
Top five, they would say diplomacy,
you know, being presidential, you know,
great aator. I don't know what else you
put in there, right? You would probably
put a few different things, you know,
good understanding of foreign affairs
and all this stuff. You know what people
are realizing from 16 to today?
Negotiation skills.
>> Yeah.
>> And the guy's a the guy's a phenomenal
negotiate. Obama wasn't a negotiator. He
was a negotiator.
>> Biden wasn't a negotiator.
>> I'm not sure Biden knew he was
president.
>> You're right. I mean, that was like a,
you know, very funny situation. So
there's a So so the part becomes Trump
uses the pulpit to speak to his allies
and enemies.
>> You know, I thought G and I were
friends. He said, but it's okay. Maybe
that's what happens. We'll see what'll
take place. I hope he's not doing it,
but if he is, I'll have a conversation
with him. Who knows what we'll do. And I
have to add, too, the Democrats have
consistently underestimated him. They
treat him like he's an idiot, like he's
some kind of a buffoon, and he's not. He
knows exactly what he
>> You still support him? You still support
him? Do you think he is?
>> You know, I I
>> If no cameras on, we're at a place, no
one's famous, people you trust, would
you say you're happy he's your president
today instead of anybody else?
>> Uh yeah, I would say that.
>> Okay.
>> I would say that. Um
>> I I have very strong feelings about the
Democrats. They're strongly negative is
what they are. Um, I believe that behind
the smiling faces and the advanced, you
know, college degrees, it's just a cabal
of criminals coming out of that Obama
administration and extending into the
Biden administration. Yes, the Trump
administration has had problems, too.
But for example, when Cash Patel was was
named FBI director, I celebrated because
the FBI's broken and it needed to be
torn down to its studs. Same with the
CIA. Now, that hasn't necessarily
happened, but at least the idea was
there, the thought was there,
>> and instead it's the Democrats that have
become the party of the status quo. It's
the Democrats that have become the party
of the of the deep state. And we need to
shake things up. I've been in Washington
for 44 years, Patrick. I moved to
Washington the week after I turned 18
years old to go to uh college. And back
then, you know, Democrats and
Republicans used to live in these group
houses up on Capitol Hill. They'd play
poker on Fridays. They'd go to church
together on Sundays. Everybody was
friends.
>> 44 is what? What year is
>> 1982?
>> Wow. So, this is pre- Reagan. This is
>> It was when Reagan was first elected. He
had been president for a year when I
moved to Washington. a time to move to
DC.
>> I'll say
>> what a time to move to DC.
>> Oh my god. And I'll tell you a funny
story. Don't think less of me. It was
really cold one night and I wanted to go
for a walk and nobody would go for a
walk with me. I lived I was going to GW
University, George Washington
University,
two blocks, three blocks from the White
House. It was December. It was cold.
Nobody wanted to go for a walk. So my
girlfriend said, "Okay, I'll go for a
walk with you." So we walk around the
White House when you could walk around
the White House. Now, it's impossible.
But we noticed that the let me think
that the west gate was open. And I said,
"Oh, something's going to happen. Let's
stand here for a second." And sure
enough, Reagan pulls out in the
presidential limousine. He's going, as
it turned out, he was going to the
Kennedy Center for the Kennedy Center
honors.
I thought that I hated Reagan at the
time. I was 18 years old, but it's the
president of the United States. So, I
started to applaud. Even though you hate
him because you were liberal at the
time.
>> He's the president. I was liberal at the
time. He's the president. I started
applying him. They stop the limousine
and he rolls the window down.
>> Stop it.
>> Mhm.
>> I got chills. Look at this.
>> I got chills thinking about it.
>> And my girlfriend's like, "Oh my god."
And so we said, "Keep [laughter]
I go, "Keep up the good work, Mr.
President, even though you're not for
him." [laughter]
>> And your girlfriend, I'm assuming, is
also not. Afterward, she's like, "You
know, you can't tell anybody that this
[laughter] just happened, right?" I
said, "I can't believe he stopped the
car."
>> Story. Did he step out or did he pull
down the window?
>> It was freezing cold. He just rolled
down the window and he said, "Thanks for
your support." Like that.
>> Wow.
>> And then years later, my brother's
visiting me from LA and we're walking
down Constitution Avenue. There used to
be like a little tiny Barnes & Noble in
the uh National Press Club at what is
that 14th and Pennsylvania Avenue. So
we're walking down the street and we
noticed two limos parked there and my
brother said, "Oh, I wonder who this
is." I said, "It's probably a cabinet
member. You see them around town all the
time." Um and he says, "Well, let's
wait. Let's wait. I want to see who it
is." I'm like, "Okay." So, we're
standing there and then out of the
Barnes & Noble comes uh Bill Clinton
with Chelsea. It's a Sunday morning.
They just went in to buy some books
[laughter]
and I didn't know what to say. So, I
just shout, "Keep abortion safe and
legal, Bill."
>> You didn't say that. [laughter] You
didn't say that.
>> And he goes, "I'm trying." And he comes
over and shakes hands.
>> He, by the way, he is the smoothest out
of all of them.
>> Oh, I've got some Clinton stories, man.
>> Do you like face to face? Like
>> face to face from my CIA days. What
happened?
>> Oh my god. I was assigned to the
American Embassy in Athens, Greece from
1998 to 2000. This is immediately after
the Monica Lewinsky scandal.
>> Woosey is Was Woosey the CI director of
CIA?
>> Woose had left
>> because he was only there for two years.
>> Yeah. He left in 94.
>> Okay. So that's after,
>> right?
>> Got it.
>> And was replaced by John Deutsch who was
horrible. So we get this notification
from the White House. The president's
going to come to Greece. We asked the
the ambassador asked it was Nick Burns
at the time. Please don't come on the
17th of November because 17 November is
the name of the big terrorist group
that's active in Greece because that's
the day that the that the U military
attacked the Athens Polytenic
University, killed dozens of students.
He comes right on the 17th of November.
It's like the worst possible day of the
year. But anyway,
the ambassador had us pulled Jobs out of
a hat. Like literally, he had a hat. And
with jobs written on scraps of paper, I
was the luckiest guy hit the lottery
that day. I pull out my job was to be
the notetaker in the president's meeting
with the prime minister.
So the meeting is at the
Intercontinental Hotel in the
presidential suite, almost the entire
top floor of the hotel. And [snorts]
it's it's Clinton, Secretary of State
Albbright, National Security Adviser
Burger, the ambassador, and me. And for
the Greeks, it was the prime minister,
the defense minister, the foreign
minister, and the Greek noteaker. So we
go there. There was a table almost the
whole length of the room just covered in
food and coffee and tea and drinks and
anything your heart desired was there.
So everybody comes in and they sit down.
I'm standing against one wall with my
notebook. The Greek uh notetaker is
standing against the opposite wall with
his notebook. And the president says to
the prime minister, "Uh, can I offer you
a cup of coffee, a tea, something to
eat?" "No." And this one says, "No."
>> The president offered a prime minister.
>> Yeah. And then he turns to me and he
says, "May I offer you something to
eat?" I said, "Oh, no, thank you, Mr.
President. I'm I'm good." And he goes,
"Are are you with me?" And I said, "Oh,
I got it."
>> I said, "Yes, sir. I'm with you." And he
said, "I thought you were Greek." And I
said, "I I kind of am, but I'm not. But
I'm with you." So, I'm ready to take
notes in this incredibly important
meeting. And it's we love you. You love
us. We have lots and lots of Greeks in
America. They own all the diners.
They're all successful.
You're the birthplace of democracy and
mathematics and medicine, and we love
you. And then the Greeks are like, we
love you, too.
when our economy couldn't handle all
these Greeks in the 20s and 30s, they
went to America and you gave them a
chance and we love you. And I'm like
waiting for something important to write
down. There's nothing. So at the end of
it, everybody stands up. They all shake
hands. Clinton hugs everybody and they
leave. Then Clinton walks out with
Albbright.
I'm sorry. Yeah, that's right. And then
Burger walks out with the ambassador. So
I walk out after them. I'm standing
about 2 feet away from Clinton and
Albbright. They finish their
conversation. Albbright goes to the
other two. So, I'm just standing there
two feet away from Clinton. And just as
she walks away, the elevator at the end
of the hall opens up and Hillary walks
off. Chelsea,
>> story's about to change.
>> She has this puss on her face like this.
She walks right up to us. And one thing
about Clinton, I I noticed it from the
very moment that I met him. He hates
silence. He wants to be joshing and
joking and laughing and telling stories
and and she's just standing there
looking at him. And so he says, "We sure
had a good time at the Parthonon this
morning, didn't we, Hill?"
She's just staring at him. So he repeats
himself, "We sure had a good time at the
Parthonon this morning, didn't we,
Hill?"
And she says, "Jesus Christ, Bill, it's
raining all day. I'll be in the room."
And she walks between us and I'm looking
at him like, "You poor man.
>> Wow.
>> You have to sleep next to that every
night." He looks right at me and he
goes, "Let's get out of here." So the
two of us walk to the elevator. The
Secret Service runs after us and then
everybody else files in. We go down to
the basement. there are 500 screaming
women from the Greek Greek American
business women's association and he gave
this rockous
you know vintage Bill Clinton it was
that Clinton magic that people used to
talk about I saw it with my own eyes
>> yeah it's it's funny that I can't tell
you how many stories of people you ask
of of Clinton Bill how many of them is
positive
>> of how he was and how it is with Hillary
we were at a
>> oh she was just awful.
>> Is that the only experience with
Hillary?
>> No, no, no. I I encountered her a number
of times after I left the agency. I was
the chief investigator on the Senate
Foreign Relations Committee and um she
had just left the committee to become
Secretary of State. So, she used to come
back all the time and she was
impossible.
Imposs
at that level. John Kerry was the one
who See, now you got me on a roll. I'm
going to be criticizing everybody, but
uh John Kerry hired me just just as he
became the chairman in January of 2009.
He called me and said, "I'm going to
reconstitute the investigative function
at the Senate Foreign Relations
Committee. Would you like to be the
investigator?" And I said, "I'd love to
be the investigator." So, he said, "I
want to make an impact. We want to, you
know, root out wrongdoing." I said,
"Great."
Nothing could have been further from the
truth. And I'll I'll tell you why if you
don't mind me rambling on for a moment.
Uh before I went up to the hill, I
struck up something of a of a
a proper friendship with M. McCclardy,
who had been Clinton's chief of staff.
Mack had partnered with Henry Kissinger
to make Kissinger Mclardy Associates.
That became Mclardy Associates. And Mack
gave me an office in his suite of
offices. It was a very generous thing to
do. So, Bill Richardson, the former
governor of New Mexico, congressman,
secretary of energy, ambassador of the
United Nations, he was also at McCclardy
Associates, and Bill and I totally hit
it off. I loved this guy. I even voted
for him for president after he dropped
out of the race.
>> Stop it.
>> I did. He's just a wonderful guy. He's
he passed away now, but he's a
wonderful, wonderful man. So, he came up
to me one day and he said, "Hey, listen.
Can you keep a secret?" I said, "Of
course." and he said, "Uh, I invited uh
I invited Obama to my house to watch the
uh Super Bowl." This was in 200 January
of 2008 before the primaries. He said at
halftime, we went for a walk and he had
like a thousand acres of wasteland out
in New Mexico. So he uh he says, "Obama,
he put his arm around my shoulder." And
he said, "Bill,
if you endorse me and you bring the
Hispanics Secretary of State," and I
said, "Oh my god, that's fantastic. It's
what Richardson always wanted." He said,
"I want you to be my deputy chief of
staff." I said, "Done. I want to be
ambassador to Greece in the second
term." And he says, "Yeah." He says,
"Great. Everybody's going to have a good
time. We're going to we're going to make
an impact." I said, "Great." I run home.
might tell my wife, "Oh my god, I'm
going to be the deputy chief of staff at
state."
So, fast forward a year and Obama wins
the election and I'm in the shower one
day. I got the radio going to listen to
the news and they said, "Former
Secretary of Energy Bill Richardson was
named by President-elect Obama today as
the Secretary of Commerce."
>> That state.
>> Uh-uh. So, I I go into the office and I
go I go, "Mr. secretary.
Congratulations. And he comes up to me.
He goes, "What the do I know about
commerce?" [laughter]
And I said, I said, "No, no, no, no.
You're looking at this wrong. We can
make this into something. There's the
Foreign Commercial Service. There's the
International Trade Representative.
Tough it out for four years. You become
Secretary of State in the second term.
This is good. We can we can make this
work."
Week later, he quits. Just drops out.
Okay. So fast forward.
>> What do you mean he drops out?
>> Yeah, he dropped out. He was never
secretary.
>> Withdrew a month later as he was being
investigated for possible improper
business dealings.
>> Yeah. They never indicted him. There
there was always this rumor that he had
done something improper. Nobody ever
could vocalize it.
>> So I I go to Capitol Hill. I become the
chief investigator on the Senate Foreign
Relations Committee. And um one thing
about John Ky, Kerry always thought that
he was smarter than everybody else. And
so his speech writers would write these
speeches and he would always go off
script and just start winging it and he
always made himself look foolish. So I
go with him to this speech at the uh
Brookings Institution and he's given the
speech, he's reading the speech and then
he goes off topic and he says, "You
know, I was supposed to be the Secretary
of State. I invited Obama over to my
house at Christmas."
>> Stop it.
>> Uh-huh. And he says, "We went for a walk
after dinner."
>> Carrie's saying this. Huh? And he says,
"Obama put his arm around my shoulder
and he said, "John, if you endorse me
and if you do it before the Kennedys do
it, Secretary of State." And he says, "I
got screwed out of it. I was supposed to
be Secretary of State." So I'm in the
front row. I'm going like this
>> to him.
>> Yeah. Like discreetly, like you're off
topic and this is not an issue you
should be talking about in public. So
afterwards he says, "I I know I
shouldn't have said that story. I know.
I And I said, Bill Richardson has
exactly the same story. I said, Barack
Obama promised half a dozen people that
they would be Secretary of State. That's
the kind of person he is. He duped all
of you guys.
Wow. So, it's not like he was telling
Bill's story. It's that Obama told this
to a bunch of people
>> and didn't keep the promise.
>> Nope. He lied to everybody.
>> Mhm.
>> Unfreakingbelievable.
Now, you wonder how much of that is a
pattern that happens often.
>> I wonder or if it was specific that if
he's some kind of sociopath. But I'll
tell you the reason why I started
telling you the story is as the
investigator,
>> he wouldn't let me investigate anything
because he didn't want to piss off
Obama. He so desperately wanted to be
Secretary of State. So, I'm doing like
the Dash Deilele massacre in northern
Afghanistan. I go to Afghanistan. I go
to Dash Leyle. They're like bones
sticking out of the ground. Still have
the clothing on them. I come back. I'm
like, "We have to investigate this."
He's like, "You're going to kill that
investigation." I said, "Senator, you're
the one who told me to go on the
investigation." Well, you know, it's it
happened a long time ago and all these
years have passed and it's time to look
forward. And it's like, okay, all right.
And then somebody emails me and says,
"Hey, uh, you know, in the new American
passports, they have these smart chips
in them." I said, "Yeah, the chips are
made in China." I said, "Seriously?
Yeah, you you have to investigate it."
So, I investigate it. I go to state. I
go to the manufacturer. All the chips
are made in China and the passports are
assembled in Thailand. They're not even
assembled in the United States. American
passports. So, I write up a memo and I
said, "Look, this this is potentially a
problem. I'm not saying the Chinese have
hacked into our passports. I'm saying
that this could be a problem. Maybe,
just maybe, we should we should
manufacture our own passports in the
United States." He's like, "Don't
release that investigation." I said,
'Why not? We don't want to embarrass the
uh embarrass the White House. I'm like,
"Are you going to let me do anything?" I
ended up resigning after two years. He
wouldn't let me do anything.
>> Because [clears throat] he wanted to be
Secretary of State.
>> Yeah. I mean, he almost became a
president until he did flip-flopping
thing. What was it? The he
>> went to one place. I don't know when it
was, but it was the flip-flopping where
it's like, "It's over for this guy." He
gave two different messages.
>> He did.
>> Was he going against Bush? He was going
against
>> Bush Bush in ' 04. And the only reason
he didn't become president was Ohio.
>> That was it was that close.
>> Didn't they go to Yale together? Yeah,
they went to Yale. They went to So what
what an interesting matchup for both of
them to be part of the Skull and Bones.
And
>> yeah, at the same time, and funny
enough, because Carrie was supposed to
be such an intellectual,
Bush's grades were better than Carrie.
>> Bush's grades were better than Carrie.
>> It was like an inside joke for us. Let
me tell you one other John Ky thing. The
first time I met him, he he called me
and invited me to come up to the office
for a conversation. So I said, "Oh, I'd
love I'd love to come up and have a
conversation." He was in the Russell
building, which is the historic Senate
office building, the oldest one. It's
where all the big hearings have been
held through history. So I go up there
and you go into his private office with
these, you know, 15 ft ceilings and
literally from the floor to the ceiling
covering an entire wall and it's about
the size of your wall here. There were
framed pictures of him with every leader
in the world from Gorbachev to the Daly
Lama,
everybody that matters. But when you
first walk in, right here on the side,
there was a credenza. It had three
things on it that struck me immediately.
One was a picture of him in an embrace
with John Lennon and they're like
goofing. Very cool. Who wouldn't want a
picture of himself with John Lennon like
that? Then on the other side it was a
picture of him with uh Peter Paul and
Mary the folk uh singers
and um and uh I knew that they were
close and he gave the eulogy at Mary
Travers funeral. And then in the middle
was a shadow box. And in the shadow box,
it had his silver star, his bronze
stars, and his purple heart. But he
famously threw those medals over the
White House fence to protest the Vietnam
War.
So I'm looking at that like what? Like
everybody knows, everybody in America
knows he threw those medals over the
White House fence. So we did the
meeting. He offered me the job and I
accepted it. And uh the chief of staff
says, "Well, how did it go?" I said, "It
went really well." He offered me the job
and I said, "Yes, but I got a question."
I said, "The shadow box with the
medals." I said, "What's up with that?
Everybody knows he threw those medals
away." And he goes, "Are you kidding?"
He said, "Those medals are the most
important things in his life." He went
to the PX that morning and he bought
copies.
>> Wow.
>> And he threw the copies over the White
House.
>> Wow. Wow.
>> I said, "Nobody in America knows that."
>> Wow. Has that story been told?
[clears throat]
>> Wow.
>> So, that was a whole, you know,
spectacle to just get
>> show.
>> Wow.
>> But it put him on the map. He ran for
lieutenant governor of uh he he ran for
Congress and lost. Ran for lieutenant
governor and won. Then ran for Congress
and won. And then when Paul Sonis
retired, uh he became a senator. Well,
you know, he'll go down as one of the
biggest heavyweights. He's a heavyweight
on on the on the Oh, yeah. You know,
Democratic side and and the bill guy
that you were talking about, I think the
bill guy was I don't know what happened
with him, but there was some recent
files that came up with him and uh
Epstein, if I'm not mistaken.
>> Yes. Oh, it broke my heart.
>> Nine times he reached out to Epstein and
whatever even after he was uh convicted
and he even visited the island. I don't
know if he including a visit to
Epstein's island. Heartbreaking.
>> Richardson scheduled meetings with Epson
as late as 2018, according to emails,
including a batch of more than 3 million
documents released.
>> Yeah. So,
>> yeah.
>> Hi everybody. I'm John Kiryaku, former
CIA officer. Please find me on MC. We
have a lot to talk about. CIA, FBI, DoD,
torture, secret prisons, international
renditions. Maybe you or your child want
to apply for a job at the CIA and are
looking for some tips. Let me know.
There's a lot we can talk about. You
pick the subject, we'll make it happen.
Again, it's on MC. Thanks and I'll see
you soon.
>> How do you handle some of this stuff
yourself? Because you you you spent a
lot of time with these guys.
>> Oh, yeah. I spent a lot of time with
these guys. You know, when I was a kid,
well, a kid when I was in college, I
used to buy this this book every two
years called The Almanac of American
Politics written by Michael Baron and
Brandt Fujimorei. It's it's the Bible of
American politics. the uh the almanac of
American politics. There it is. And I
was just so thrilled to be in
Washington, going to school in
Washington. Every Friday, I never had
Friday classes. So every Friday, I'd
take my almanac of American politics.
I'd go to Capitol Hill and I'd get
autographs from congressmen and
senators.
>> At what age?
>> 18.
And I was working for my congressman,
Congressman Joe Coulter. He was a
conservative Democrat from Western
Pennsylvania. pro-life, pro- gun, pro-
labor, the old school kind of Democrat.
>> Got it.
>> And um he came into the office one day.
The the woman I was sitting next to, she
was engaged to a lobbyist. He happened
to be standing there. And the
congressman came in the office one day
and he goes, "I got laid last night."
And because I was an innocent kid, I
turned to the woman and I said, "He's
lying. Mrs. Coulter's in Pittsburgh
right now." And I was like, "Oh
Mrs. Coulter's in Pittsburgh right now."
[laughter]
And then the lobbyist said to me,
"Buddy, you got to stop idolizing these
guys. They're all scumbags." And they
all put their pants on one leg at a
time.
>> Wow.
>> And that was the first time that I ever
started putting these people on Capitol
Hill into perspective. Who who was the
one that at least maintained some uh
strong character and values and
principles?
>> That was John McCain.
John McCain became a hero for me.
>> John McCain really
>> of all people. I know I know people
people kind of look at me oddly every
time I say this, but just as an example,
six weeks before I got out of prison, I
I was allowed to call my wife every
other day for 15 minutes. So, six weeks
before I got out of prison, I called her
and I said, "How's your day?" She said,
"It's great." And I said, "Really? Why
great? What made it so great?" And she
said, "The Senate torture report was
released today and it proved that
everything you said was true." And she
said, "John McCain got up on the floor
of the Senate and he named you by name
and he said that if it wasn't for you,
the American people would have never had
any idea what the CIA was doing in their
name." This is the water boarding.
>> The water boarding. Yeah.
>> That you became the whistleblower. And I
think Obama Obama's after you, right? He
prosecuted six of you guys. He he is
>> eight more than all the presidents
combined.
>> Three times all previous presidents
combined
>> in American history.
>> Unfreaking believe. The Espionage, Was
it the Espionage Act?
>> Espionage Act.
>> So you were the sixth out of the eight.
>> I was the sixth out of the eight. The
Espionage Act was written in 1917
to combat German saboturs during the
First World War.
Between 1917 and 2009, three people were
prosecuted for speaking to the press.
Just under Obama, eight of us were
Eight of us. I remember a friend of mine
at the White House saying, "Be careful
of this guy. Obama has what his words
Obama has a Nixonian obsession
with national security leaks. And I said
why? He said because John Brennan's
whispering in his ear every single day,
prosecute, prosecute, prosecute. So he
did
>> eight times. So you you're going through
your wife 15 minutes. Hey, you won't
believe McCain had your back. McCain,
you know, got up on you, named you.
>> And when I got out of prison, well, you
know what? Before when I was working for
Carrie, Car's office was directly next
door to McCain's in in the Russell
building. And every time Carrie and I
would be walking out of the out of the
office like for a vote, McCain would be
walking out of his office and he would
always go out of his way to come and
shake my hand. How are you, John? I'd
say doing well, senator. How are you
doing? And we would always shake hands.
And then Carrie one time said, "Why
don't you and McCain get a room or
something?" And I said, "No, no, he's
he's serious. He's a sincere guy. They
had this weird lovehate relationship
between they respected each other, but
they didn't like each other. And I said,
"No, McCain's a a sweetheart. He really
is." When I got out of prison, this is
this is the especially painful part. I
got out of prison. I was out four or
five days, and I get a call from a guy
on McCain's staff,
a very serious guy, and he says,
"Senator McCain says, "Welcome home."
and he wants to know how he can be
helpful to you. And I said, 'Oh my god.
Tell him thank you so much. He can be
helpful by giving me my pension back. I
said, "These Obama people confiscated my
pension. 20 years of proud government
service."
>> This is a $780,000.
>> Correct.
>> Yep.
>> So
my attorney, who's also one of my best
friends, was the deputy attorney general
under Reagan, and he said, "I have an
idea." We went up to meet with McCain's
people. He wrote an amendment and it was
hilarious. It was like one sentence and
it said, "Every American
who had his pension confiscated
for violating the Intelligence
Identities Protection Act between
October 1st and October 31st, 2012 shall
hereby have that pension reinstated."
I'm the only person in the world. So
McCain says, "I'm going to slip this
into the National Defense Authorization
Act." He said, "That thing's like 3,000
pages long. Nobody reads them." He said,
"I'm going to put it down in the bottom.
Nobody's going to pay any attention.
We're going to get you your pension
back." So he said, I said, "Well, but
it's going to be in the Senate version.
It's not going to be in the House
version." He said, "I'll get myself
appointed to the conference committee
and I'll ensure that it is in there in
the final bill." And then he got brain
cancer.
And so he couldn't be on the conference
committee. He was too sick. And so they
pulled it out. And
>> three pages all the way in the back and
they pulled it out. The 780.
>> And they pulled it out. So here.
>> So for you, McCain is number one on the
list. Go with the stuff that we're
talking about, the espionage act. Yeah.
>> And the stuff that Obama did, go to FISA
because FISA
>> goes back to what FISA starts off with
Teddy Ted Kennedy if I'm not mistaken.
Yeah. and he pitches it and he proposes
it and I think Carter comes in and the
concern at the time this is right after
Watergate if I'm not mistaken it's like
hey this is the way for us to catch
terrorists
>> and then Obama ends up using that to go
after people like you and also going
after people like Trump and then we're
seeing
>> look at Carter Page the poor guy they
ruined his life
>> you know you make a very important point
here that bears repeating FISA is not
new FISA has been around since the
Carter administration.
Um Ted Kennedy was instrumental in the
passage of FISA. Um they believed back
then that there was a real danger of you
know foreign involvement in American
political machinations.
And so they passed FISA that would allow
this secret court that sits on the top
floor of the Justice Department. It's
off limits to everybody. the judges are
constantly rotating in and out. They're
they're sitting federal district court
judges from around the country and um
the CIA and the FBI can go there and say
we need a secret warrant to tap the
phones of you know X Y and Z people and
they get it and there's nothing in
writing nothing that can ever be
released to the American people. So you
don't have any idea if maybe there's a
FISA warrant on you. There's not
supposed to be because you're an
American citizen, but so is Carter Page.
These are supposed to be warrants on
foreign nationals in touch with
Americans.
Well, you know, when the FISA court
turns down something like whatever it
is, 19100s of 1% or whatever, where's
the oversight?
Who exists in government to say, "Wait a
minute, this is wrong. You're abusing
this program." To make it worse, section
702 is being debated right now. Section
702 is something that has to come up for
reauthor reauthorization every two
years. And what section 702 does is it
allows these continued secret here it is
secret warrantless
uh wire taps on people. But again, you
know, on whom and what's the threshold?
We don't know what the threshold is.
Nobody will tell us. And so you get
somebody like Carter Page who,
you know, was doing what he thought he
was supposed to be doing as a, you know,
mid-level Trump campaign person talking
to an Australian ambassador and the next
thing you know, he knows, well, he
didn't know it actually. The next thing
he is experiencing is he's under
investigation. there are FISA warrants
against him and then the FISA warrants
were repeatedly renewed even though
there was no evidence that he he had
ever committed a crime. I believe I
think many Americans believe that this
was done at the behest of uh of John
Brennan and it was all part of Brennan's
plan
to deny Donald Trump the presidency. I
really honestly believe that that's what
this is.
>> Well, they failed miserably. They failed
miserably and now it's going to be their
turn to have the tables turned.
>> And you think they're going to use it?
>> God, I hope so. Um, you know, there
there has been news this week about uh
>> cash you're talking about, you know,
Todd Blanch, what they're doing. Yeah.
>> I'm genuinely worried now that they're
not going to prosecute John Brennan. I
think John Brennan is a malevolent
figure in modern American politics and
government. John Brennan, I believe, um,
really did attempt to carry out a coup,
not with tanks in the streets. He tried
to do it through rumor and innuendo.
And he tried to deny Donald Trump the
presidency. He tried to deny, you know,
the choice of 51% of Americans.
>> Yeah. So DOJ's uh US abruptly resends.
>> Yeah. Day before yesterday. I'm deeply
worried about this.
>> What's their reasoning? What argument
did they give?
>> They didn't give a reason. They just did
it.
Just as they they named Joe Deg Geneva.
Do you remember Joe Deg Geneva? He was a
US attorney under Reagan. He's a real
go-getter. like a real thinker. Uh but
he's kind of, you know, he's an older
guy now. He's in his 80s.
>> De Geneva.
>> Yeah. Joseph De Geneva. Um strong Trump
supporter.
And um
just at the beginning of uh of the week,
he was named the lead investigator in
the Brennan case in South Florida,
>> which was great. He's a giant.
But then all of a sudden these subpoenas
were rescended.
>> Why do you think?
>> Speculate. Why do you think?
>> I've been told that the
alleged crimes
that are being investigated are what are
called process crimes. Crimes you and I
probably already committed three, four
times today without even knowing it. Um
those are really hard to prosecute
because then you have to argue criminal
intent. And you know, one of them is is
uh lying to Congress. Yeah, that's a
crime. Almost nobody gets prosecuted.
All the Trump people did because the
Democrats, you know, lost their minds at
the end of the first Trump term. Um but
that's one of those ones that, you know,
grand juries are kind of loathed to to
put people in prison for.
I have argued
that the Justice Department should
looking at should be looking at a uh
conspiracy charge because clearly there
was a conspiracy to deny Trump the
presidency. And if there is a
conspiracy, just the fact that you're
covering up the conspiracy ought to be
enough to reset the statute of
limitations literally every single day.
And that's a serious crime. That's, you
know, you could get 10 years in prison,
20 years in prison, whatever it is, for
conspiracy.
Yeah, part of it I'm thinking so the
FISA if you know concerns some people
well you know he could have stopped it
why didn't he stop the FISA and you know
he knows this isn't you know what's
going to happen for the next president
to come in that they're going to
investigate but then the party you have
to think about to say
>> so you want me to stop it now after they
used it against me
>> right
>> so
>> but you know I think it's even I think
that his thinking is even more pure than
that it's not just you know, they used
it against me. He said something this
week that I was like, "Oh, okay. I've
seen other presidents, you know, kind of
fall into this in the past." He said he
talked to three dozen generals and
admirals and every single one of them
said, "We need FISA 702 because it keeps
America safe." I personally think that
that's not exactly true. I think it
should be tightened so that the civil
liberties of Americans are protected.
But I think that three dozen generals
and admirals did tell him that
>> this is a week. This is the one you're
talking about here. Yeah. This is it.
>> When the dirty cop James Comey failed
the head of uh failed head of FBI went
after me. He was using FISA title one
the domestic collection not FISA 702
>> the foreign collection which needs to be
extended today. While parts of FISA were
illegally and unfortunately used against
me and the Democrats disgraceful which
fund an attack in a Russia Russia Russia
hoax and perhaps would be used against
me in the future. willing to risk the
giving up of my rights and privileges as
a citizen for our great military and
country, our military patriots,
desperately need FISA 702 and it is one
of the reasons we have such tremendous
success on the battlefield. I've spoken
with many military leaders who say FISA
is necessary in order to protect our
troops overseas as well as our people
here at home from the threat of foreign
terror attacks. It has already prevented
many such attacks.
>> See, but that's kind of apples and
oranges.
It's if FISA 702 isn't leading to
battlefield field victories. FISA 702 is
identifying individuals or small groups
of people who are planning terrorist
attacks overseas.
That's why we need FISA 702. What we
don't need is the CIA, the FBI, and NSA
then saying, "Huh, this Patrick Bet
David guy, he looks like an interesting
character. We're going to check him
out." Why? Why are they checking you
out? You're an American citizen. You
have constitutional rights.
You know, Tucker Carlson, he's talking
to, you know, a Russian to interview
Putin. He's talking to an Iranian to
interview Pzeskian or whomever he he
interviewed.
>> What? They're going to He's not allowed.
He's a journalist. He can interview
anybody he wants. So, there's no reason
to use 702 against American citizens
like that. We need We need tighter
controls.
>> You think we're going to see something?
You think we're going to see something
them going after anybody? Comey,
Clinton's, anything.
>> Obama.
>> I don't
>> nothing.
>> No, I think it's wishful thinking.
>> So, no one's getting arrested. No one's
going to be
>> Well, especially not Obama because these
recent Supreme Court decisions clearing
Trump also, you know, through the back
door cleared Obama of just about
anything that he's been accused of
doing. So, Obama, I think, is free and
clear. Hillary, I've actually looked
into this. The statute of limitations
has expired on just about everything
that you could possibly accuse Hillary
of doing. So I think she's scott-free as
well.
John Brennan, however, like I said, this
is a very bad guy. This is a guy I I've
known John Brennan for 35 36 years. He's
a bad guy. And we need controls on what
some of these intelligence people or
former intelligence people are able to
do. You remember, do you remember in the
first term when President Trump
suspended the security clearances of the
51 signitories
>> to the Hunter Biden?
>> None of those people should have had
security clearances in the first place.
If you if you retire from the CIA and
then you go to MSNBC to be a talking
head, why in God's name do you have a
security clearance?
>> Still.
>> Still. What do you need a security
clearance for? So you can parro it back
on MSNBC. Uh-uh. No. Once you walk out
that door on your last day, that should
be the end of it. Unless you're
transferring to a defense contractor
where they can hold your clearance and,
you know, work with CIA security and you
do classified work. That's different.
That's how people make a living. But to
go to the media, not a chance. None of
them should have had security
clearances. I'll tell you what, I knew
every single one of the 51 of them that
signed that letter. Every single one of
them. None of them should have had a
security clearance.
>> Why do you say that?
>> Because they became political people.
>> Got it,
>> Pat. time was. You're going to laugh
when I tell you this.
When I first joined the CIA, I had
literally no idea the political
affiliations of the people that I sat
with 10 hours a day. No idea. It never
came up. It never needed to come up. We
were there to serve the American people.
In 1996,
I sat like three cubicles down from this
woman who very discreetly put up a Bob
Dole for president bumper sticker in her
cubicle. They came down on her like a
ton of bricks. She was suspended for a
week without pay. She was denied
promotion for a year and they put a
letter in her file saying that she had
violated agency regulations. She I
remember her balling as she was walking
out
>> sticker of Bob
>> a sticker.
>> So politics was verboten at the CIA. Now
they're signing letters and going on TV
and you know jumping into campaigns.
Every single one of those 51 people was
working for Hillary Hillary Clinton
either directly or indirectly. Every
single one of them.
>> That was unheard of. And and this is how
John Brennan became somebody because
John Brennan was was a nobody
around 2007.
There was a gigantic exodus of people
from the senior intelligence service at
the CIA. 911 was six years behind us.
People decided to retire. There they
are. People decided to retire.
And so
almost
well they were pretty much split 50/50
down the middle. Half of them went to
the Hillary campaign, half of them went
to the McCain campaign. For whatever
reason, John Brennan was the only one
that went to the Obama campaign. And
then lo and behold, Obama wins the
thing. So he's the guy. And that's how
he became somebody. He wasn't any
smarter than anybody else. He was just
better placed for a year and he turned
it into something
>> gained a lot of power
>> and that was the problem. Destroyed a
lot of people's lives.
>> He gained he gained a lot of power,
destroyed a lot of people's lives and
people have long memories and now the
tables are turned
>> if they do something. I mean the reality
is if they do something which
>> you know them okay. Okay. So to me, the
way I process this with FISA on on why
they're why they're doing this. It's an
insurance policy to keep everybody in
check for the next two and a half years.
>> Yeah,
>> that's one the way I look at it because
at the end of the day, what's your
overunder if you're a gambling man? What
is [clears throat] the likelihood that
the president is going to pardon
everybody, including his family, the
last month before he leaves office?
>> I hope he does.
>> So 90%.
I I I Yeah, I hope so.
>> I think so, as well.
>> I hope so. I think so. And I'll tell you
why. I'm biased. And I will freely admit
my bias.
>> Oh, I didn't see that. Thank you for
that.
>> Trump promises mass pardons to staff
before leaving office. I I have been
working very hard to get in front of the
president, figuratively speaking,
because I've asked for a pardon. I I
filed the paperwork. I did all the right
things. I've talked to everybody I can
possibly talk to. Yesterday I discovered
Do you know what Kelshi is?
>> Of course.
>> So I discovered my name on Kelshi. Like
how how likely is it that I'm going to
be pardoned?
>> Really?
>> Yeah. And
>> so there's a Kelshi on you.
>> Yeah. And it's actually my odds are
pretty good. My odds were 20% the other
day.
>> Uh there I am. 19%.
It wouldn't let me bet because it said I
have a conflict of income. [laughter]
>> I tried to put 20 bucks and it said no.
>> How much money has been volume is
$152,000. So it's a real it's a real
thing.
>> Yeah, it's a real thing.
>> Okay.
>> So I'm I'm praying to God every night
that um that Donald Trump wakes up and
say and says this Kiryaku guy, he the
Obama people screwed him and Brennan
screwed him. You know, I I had I had
five seconds with the president at Mara
Lago. a year and a half ago,
uh, I went with a friend of mine for
lunch and sure enough the president
walks in, everybody politely politely
applauds and he, you know, waves and
sits down. He has lunch. He was with
Mark Zuckerberg and um, finally he gets
up and they tell you when you're walking
in, I know you've been there, they tell
you when you're walking in, um, no
pictures, no videos, no hats, and don't
ever approach the president. If he wants
to talk, he'll approach you. So, I'm
with my buddy. we both want pardons. And
uh [laughter]
very honest, we're here for a pardon.
And so he gets up and I'm like, "Oh my
god, he's going to come over here." So
he comes over to our table. I jump up
and I said, "Mr. President, um my name's
John Kiryaku. I'm the CIA torture
whistleblower." And then I I used my my
go-to line. I said, "Barack Obama and
John Brennan ruined my life, and you
were the only person who can give it
back to me." And he goes like this. He
goes,
"Tucker Carlson told me about you." And
I said, "Yes, sir." Tucker's been a
great supporter and Judge Npalitano, Dr.
Phil, couple other people that I
mentioned, they they wrote a letter and
he said, "Uh" he said, "Talk to Pam
Bondi. She'll get the paperwork done." I
said, "Thank you, Mr. President." He
moves on. I didn't have any path to Pam
Bondi. Um I have, you know, a friend of
a friend of a friend of Pam Bondi and
nothing happened. But, you know, I've
been able to speak with the US pardon
attorney, a lovely, lovely man um named
Ed Martin and a couple of other people
close to the president. But there I
there's literally nothing else I can do.
I don't know what to do.
>> What would a pardon do to your life?
>> It would give me my my pension back.
>> That's it.
>> And give me my gun rights back, Pat. I I
I want my guns back.
>> So, wait a minute. You don't have you
can't you haven't been able to carry
since.
>> Felon with a gun is a mandatory 5-year
minimum. mandatory five-year minimum.
Felon with a gun is a mandatory
five-year minimum.
>> No questions asked, straight to prison,
five years.
>> So, you So, you want your second
amendment rights back and you want your
pension back? Yes.
>> So, if you get the pardon, what's the
next step for you? Do you just go in and
say, "I got the pardon. Can I get my uh
uh pension?"
>> I I My kids and I have talked about
this. I said, "We're all piling in the
car and we are driving directly to the
gun show at Dulles Airport Expo Center
[laughter]
with wads of cash and I'm buying guns."
>> Good for you. So, two things. Pension
and guns.
>> Pension and guns.
>> It the There's a third thing, but I've
dealt with it. Um, I lost my voting
rights for life. So,
I I was going through the process like
how do I get my voting rights back?
Terry McAuliff was the governor of
Virginia at the time. So, I went online,
Virginia Secretary of State's office.
Are you a felon? Yes. I want my my
voting rights back. I fill out the form
and I just send it in. It says, "You'll
hear in two weeks." Well, like 3 4 weeks
passed and I hadn't heard anything. So,
I just called the toll-free number and
the guy's like, "Okay, what's your
social security number?" So, I told him
and he's like, "Oh, oh." Like, he sees
on the screen, "Right, yes, you're in
process, so just hang on." I said, "Oh,
okay. Thank you. Great." I hang up. Like
a week later, 7:00 in the morning, my
doorbell rings. I was getting the kids
ready for school. So, I go to the door.
Like, who in the world's going to be at
the door at 7:00 in the morning, and
it's a courier from the governor's
office. He's got this big envelope, this
like hard cardboard envelope, and it's a
decree with the big gold seal. It's a
state pardon. I hadn't even applied for
a pardon, but Terry McAuliffe, God bless
him. I never met the man, but he
pardoned me. He must have followed my
case, and so I got my state gun rights
back, which is a nice gesture,
>> but what? I buy a gun, I get arrested,
and I say, "Well, the state of Virginia
allows me to carry a gun." Yeah, but
Washington DC doesn't. So, five years
mandatory minimum
>> still with that. Yeah. Well, interesting
that that uh I mean your story was
everywhere when you when you came out.
It's not like it it was the story for I
don't know how long when everybody
around the world was following it
>> last night. Uh I'm showing my uh my
wife. I said, "So who are you talking
to?" I said, "John Kira is coming back."
Oh, really? Yeah. So tell me a little
bit more about John. I said, "Babe, this
is Let me tell you what he was known
for. Waterboarding." says, "My wife, who
is not following everything that's going
on, she's not one that's follows
everything politically,"
she says, "Tell me more about
waterboarding." We went and pulled up a
clip of Chris, is it?
>> Oh, Chris Hitchens.
>> Chris Hitchens
>> who said, "Water boarding is nothing.
Waterboarding is not a big deal." Have
you ever seen this clip, Rob? He's
laying there and they put a towel over
him. He says, "I'll be able to breathe."
[laughter]
>> And he tries to do waterboarding
himself. You got to fast forward it
because it's a fiveminute clip. Keep
going. Keep going. Keep going. It's uh
uh I think that's the part where he
jumps up. Yeah, this is it. Can we even
show this? Well, let's do it anyways.
So, they're waterboarding him. He said
he lasted 17 seconds right there. 17
seconds.
[laughter]
And you know what he said? Do you know
what happened afterwards?
for the rest of his life.
>> Every time he couldn't breathe for a
second, he would have panic attacks.
>> Yes.
>> Because of the impact of water boarding
had on him.
>> That's right.
>> And that's Chris Hitchens, which is
like, "Oh, there's
>> big babies."
>> Yes.
>> Big babies. So,
>> yeah. So, listen, you know, it'll be
interesting to see what Yeah, that's
right. Believe me, it's torture.
>> I remember when that came out.
>> Yeah. 08 when he said this. Let's talk
about SPLC. So C Patel and Todd Blanch
dropped this, right? And SPLC, you know,
maybe at the beginning their reasoning
was noble and they've raised god knows
how much money. We saw reports of who's
given him money. George Clooney gave him
money. Tim Cook gave him a million
bucks. I think Chase gave him money.
Soros was speculated to have given him
money. And then you see the 2019 Charity
Watch, it's a leftist organization, gave
SPLC an F. Current affairs gave SPLC an
outright fraud that uses fear to cause
leftists to write checks. Liberal death
penalty abolitionist Steven Bright, I
think is his name, refused to take an
award from SPLC said the SPLC has been
running a uh been running been run by a
con man and a fraud. And then former
SPLC employees in 2019 told the New
Yorker that we were part of the con and
we knew it. Like they knew they were
doing this. What what do you know about
it? And why is this such a big deal of
what happened?
>> Well, when I first saw the push
notification that the SPLC was being
indicted on felonies, multiple felonies,
>> my first thought was, "Oh, come on. We
have nothing better to do." And then I
clicked on it and I read the article and
I said, "Oh, These are real
crimes." Real crimes. The kind of crimes
where they're documentary. You either
did it or you didn't do it. And if
they've got documentary evidence that
they did it, this could be the end of
the SPLC.
>> Literally,
>> I think it could be.
>> Well, so I'm watching the opposition to
see what their argument is. You know,
the current president reacted. I don't
know if you saw his clip or not. He
said, "Yeah, you know what? You know how
they're spinning it? Here's what they're
saying. They're saying this is so unfair
because this was our way of paying
informants
to learn more about the organization." I
knew they were going to say, "That like
journalists who buy one share of stock
so that they can go to the the stock."
Yes.
>> Holders meeting and you know
>> they're spinning it in a way to say
shame on them to do this. These are
people that are doing great work. That
was the guy who responded uh claiming
that's what they're doing in the past.
So what do what what do you think about
that?
>> Um I think that that is weak because
what they're being accused of doing is
giving money to the Ku Klux Clan, giving
money to Nazi groups, you know,
laundering money. There are very clear
laws, very specific laws about money
laundering. You know, you can't do it.
You can't do it. And so, why launder it
in the first place? Again,
what the Justice Department is accusing
them of doing is is documented.
And so, they're going to have their day
in court just like everybody else. Uh,
and they can they can make that argument
certainly.
>> Yeah. I saw lists of uh Moms of Liberty
was on that group. I think we had uh the
leader of Moms of Liberty on the
podcast, Rob, if I'm not mistaken. She
was phenomenal.
>> They had TPUSA on that list. They had
>> right
>> uh uh uh different uh groups. Um but
they didn't have Antifa on that group.
They didn't have And even there's a Rob
go to go to uh what's his name? Staceil
uh uh John Staceil. Can you go on
YouTube and go to John Staceil? I want
to give him credit on this. John Staceil
has done a lot of work on SPLC and just
type in SPLC if you could. Just type in
SPLC John Staceil one from two years
ago. That one right there. Go to about
minute uh and we'll give credit to John
if you want to go subscribe to his
channel. Rob, let's make sure we put the
link below as well. So if people want to
go support him. Uh so John Staceil go
about minute. Keep going. Keep going.
Keep going. I'll tell you. Keep going.
Keep going. Keep going. About minute
four. So keep going. No, that's not
minute. That's minute one. Keep going.
Minute four. Rob, keep going.
Keep going. Um, he's as Okay, right
there. Press play. Watch what they find
here.
>> Go ahead.
>> Which is in offshore accounts, Caymans,
and places like that.
>> How do you know?
>> Oh, we look at their 990. Pause it right
there.
>> Ah, the 990.
>> The 990 shows that they were taking
money. Press play. It's going to show
>> islands
>> right there. Now, the Southern Poverty
Law Center calls groups that simply
oppose sexually explicit content in
schools anti-government extremists. Moms
for Liberty and Moms for America are on
the hate map because they dare do things
like seek school board seats to try to
stop districts from disregarding
opinions. Now,
>> keep in mind is not a Republican. He's a
libertarian.
>> No, no, he's a libertarian. He's a
libertarian one. A very well-known one.
Yeah. So, you know, if this goes I I I
wonder what the positioning is going to
be. I wonder who's going to come out
defending them. How much money did they
have in the account? I don't know why I
saw they went from 50 million to 100
million to 200 million.
>> Oh my god.
>> What is the uh uh uh how much total
money have they raised? What's the total
amount of I don't know why I saw 720
million. Maybe that was a uh have they
total raised? They've raised a lot of
money. Oh, there you go. Okay. uh total
assets in 2024. Look at that.
>> 786.7
and some reports noting it's 822. When I
saw 720 million, I said they cannot be
that powerful. Their endowment was 822.
Shocking.
>> Look at the kind of power you have with
that. What you could do.
>> Wow. Yeah. That's incredible. I got to
say also on the 990s, I was the king of
the 990s at the Senate Foreign Relations
Committee. The 990s will tell you
everything you need to know about an
organization that you're targeting
because to keep themselves out of
trouble, they admit to everything
thinking nobody's ever going to look at
the 990.
>> So you guys looked at the 990s.
>> Most most organizations
actually have it on their on their web
page. It's oftentimes hidden. There was
only one time that I wanted to see a 990
that wasn't publicly available and I
just called the organization and I said,
"I'm I'm the chief investigator from the
Senate Foreign Relations Committee and I
need to see your 990." And they were
like, "Please don't." And I said, "No,
I'm going to swing by. I'll give you a
day. I'm going to swing by and pick it
up." And their their 990 must have been
150 pages long. I had never seen one
more than a page or two. It was 150
pages long. I found nothing wrong with
it and I just dropped the investigation.
>> So the 990 is what? It's a document that
most tax exempt organizations file every
year.
>> Yep.
>> With the IRS. It tells the government
and the public how the n how the
nonprofit operates financially.
>> Yep. It's got everything. It's like the
crown jewel of the of the uh the tax
forms.
>> So So okay, Rob, can you pull up who
else gave SPLC money? Who are the
biggest contributors
contributors of SPLC?
I'm actually curious. I've seen some of
the names.
>> Tim Cook, Million Bucks, George Soros.
>> Wow. George.
>> So, it took $106 million in donations
just in 2024.
786. It funnel through it. Um I'm
wondering, yeah, I got the Soros. I got
the Clooney. I got the Tim Tim Cook.
Charles Schwab charitable foundation.
Fidelity Charitable gave a lot of money.
National philanthropic.
Yeah, I'm reading a book right now on
charities because you know when you
gets to a point where family offices
need to start charities and all this
other stuff. The book I'm reading today,
it tells a story of never ever start a
charity and leave the board to decide
what to do with the money because
whatever cause you start today,
>> yeah,
>> you're going to lose control with the
way it is and 10 years later they can
change the cause they want to support.
>> So maybe your cause was one thing, 10,
20, 30 years later it could change to
something else. So, by the way, let me
ask you if you worked if you still were
at the CIA today
>> and you got the call from the director
of CIA and they said, you know, John, I
want you to go find out because there's
so much noise right now in the
marketplace. I want you to go find out
who is actually taking money from
Israel, who's taking money from Qatar
Qatar, who's taking money from these
different organizations,
whether they are trying to get people to
give pro- Zionist messaging or trying to
give pro-Islam, you know, it's Sharia is
not that bad, everything's okay, or
socialism. How quickly would you be able
to find out if someone's getting funded
or not?
I I I get that it's a hypothetical
question. It's an FBI issue. The CIA by
law would be forbidden from doing that
on Americans, but uh but you could
certainly look at uh at foreign
nationals. CIA could look at foreign
nationals. You you probably need a
couple of months to really dig it up,
but you could dig it up.
>> Would you be able to find out for a fact
like if if
>> not all of it?
>> So the reason why I'm asking is because
I had Dominic Tarjinski here. He is a EU
parl member of the parliament and he
tells the story of in 2022 these
multiple EU parliament members were
caught getting ah
>> uh uh what do you call it
>> oh yeah big suffion
>> one of them was Greek and she she's in
prison now yes
>> yeah $1 and half million dollars of cash
can you go to that one Rob where it's
which one is this one is this the one
>> yeah So, $1.5 million. But go to if you
can go to uh the picture. Yeah, that's
the lady right there. Whatever her name
is. She was part of the corruption. And
apparently there was so much money in
one of the duffel bags that they dropped
$60,000 $60,000 that they caught
afterwards where cash was being given.
And then when you go even deeper, you
find that the history of, you know,
nowadays, you know, uh, King Charles is
very pro-Islamist,
you know, pro, it's not nothing wrong
with that. Everything is fine. And then
there were reports about him taking $3.2
million. I don't know if you've seen
that report.
>> Like he needs the money.
>> Like he needs the money, but he took
$3.2 million.
>> You know, I hate to say it, Pat.
>> Right there. Look at this. From between
2011 and 2015, then Prince Charles
received approximately 3.2 $.2 million
in cash payments from Qatari prime
minister. This has been confirmed and he
said he did but he said the moment money
went into our account we just gave it to
charity immediately. There was no
illegal things done. You know we're
supposed to believe that. So I wonder
the you know buying influence if if the
government all of a sudden I don't even
know if they would pursue this because
because you know they may not even want
that man I if somebody was to come out
like let's just say they did this with
SPLC.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And all of a sudden they
come out and say, "Let me tell you guys
that these top 50 influencers, who's
funding them, who they're getting money
from, it would silence the entire market
and it would the fog of war in
mainstream media and podcast and today
would be gone. Everybody would say,
"Okay, we know why you say what you say.
We know where your position is. Great.
Can we all move on? Let's move forward."
>> This is exactly why we need robust
oversight rather than the cheerleaders
on Capitol Hill that we have. We need
people who are really going to provide
independent oversight. Let me tell you a
story and forgive me that I have to sort
of fudge the language a little bit, but
I I need to I had a conversation with a
senator a couple of days ago. Um he uh
had somebody reach out. Can you come up
to the office? I said, of course. I go
up there and he's concerned about
some documents. He needed to see some
documents. documents that were
classified in the 1970s.
>> I said, "Well, they they should have
been subject to mandatory
declassification. We have a mandatory
declassification law in this country
after 30 or 35 years. They have to be
declassified unless they contain the
names of a source or um the methods of
an ongoing operation." And he said,
"Exactly." And they've never been
declassified. And he said, "I went to
the CIA and they said, "We don't know
what you're talking about. They're not
our documents." And it turns out that
they're Senate documents. Well, the
Senate is not sub the the Congress is
not subject to the Freedom of
Information Act and it's not subject
they always exempt themselves from their
own laws, right? So no laws apply on
Capitol Hill. They do anything they
want. And so I said, uh, well, why don't
you go to leadership? And he said, I
went to leadership and they said they
don't want to get involved in this fight
between two committee chairman. And I
said, ' And the other chairman, he said,
'The other chairman told me to go screw
myself.
And I said, 'Are you kidding me?' And he
said, 'n no.' He said, 'I don't know
what to do.
And we sat there for two hours and we
could not come up with a plan. And it's
because there is no oversight.
It's funny to me. You read the
Constitution, the Constitution says that
that the government is made up of three
co-equal branches. the executive, the
legislative, and the judicial. But
that's just not how we treat it. The the
the the
legislative has seated its authority to
the executive. And so now, if you know
there's a Republican in the White House,
Republicans on Capitol Hill are going to
do everything they can to support the
the president and to pass the
president's legislation. The Democrats
have somebody in the White House. The
Democrats in Congress are going to do
everything they can to support the
president. That's not what the founding
fathers envisioned. Three co-equal
branches and then what [clears throat]
we end up with is these so-called
oversight committees that don't oversee
anything.
They just egg them on.
>> Yeah. So, I think I think the the part
with America that when when I hear
people that are tired, I'm like, what
are you tired with? What are you most
upset with? I just don't think there's
any accountability. That's exactly the
problem.
>> Yeah. I just don't think there's any
accountability. What do you mean? It
seems like they're all on the same
party. Seems like they all protect. You
hear that message, right? You can't have
that because that's not good in a
democracy if there's accountability for
the average person that does something
and then there isn't for the other guys.
What are you talking about? Yeah. No,
there's not. So, I I I
think this administration
uh a story came out. I don't know if you
saw the story came out yesterday saying
that uh again it's a leak that they want
Tulsi to resign after midterms.
>> Okay. So they want Tulsi to resign after
midterms. All right. That story was
leaked. I don't know if it's even a
story there or not. There you go. Yeah.
Director Donald Trump reportedly wants
to direct their national. Okay. Who
knows what these stories are? Like we
asked you earlier, what stories do they
leak? What do they not? And you kind of
test the market.
>> Who knows what this is, you know, on on
how they're dropping a story. But to me,
if there's anything, this administration
has a shot at increasing the score the
people have in the CIA, in the FBI, in
the US government a little bit more
because the way it dropped after Kennedy
is a
>> oh my god,
>> it's like a massive from 72% trust in
the FBI. Can you pull up the history of
trust in the US government or trust in
the FBI or trust in the CIA
>> and then Watergate? [clears throat] And
then Watergate, you know, one by one by
one. Um, there's a chart, Rob. If you go
back and just go to images, you'll see
it. Yeah, it's one of those that shows
the high was 72% and I don't know what.
Yeah. Zoom in a little bit if you could.
Oh, it doesn't go all the way back. It
doesn't go all the way back. So, that
goes from 97. The one I'm looking at is
from the 60s, you know. Uh, uh, go on
the second one. See what the the Pew
Research. There you go. That's the one
from 58.
>> Wow. Look at that. We used to trust 72%.
>> Look at that.
>> We used to trust the government. We're
like, "Yeah, they're good." You know,
they're And then we're now in the 20s
and the teens and that's 15. I would
assume it's even lower today.
>> Like even 911, it was barely 50%.
>> Yep. Yep. That's right. Even 911 was
50%. At least we're like, "Look, wow.
>> They're the good people. They're here to
protect us."
>> Yeah. that there is a massive mass. And
by the way, I think long-term, the lower
that score goes, you you you you cannot
risk not knowing the consequences of the
score getting too low.
>> That's right.
>> Cuz if it gets too low, then what does
the youth do who don't have anything to
lose? Anything. The youngest willing to
break the whole thing because they're
like, "Well, you know what? You guys are
not doing anything. You guys are all
protecting each other. You guys are
>> wow."
>> And then you're dealing with a bigger
problem. I hope they do something to
regain the faith. Are you following the
story with the scientists? Are you kind
of
>> So, you know, Rob,
>> at first I'll admit to you, at first I
was like, "Oh, come on. Another
conspiracy theory." And then I started
reading and I was like, "Oh,
>> you think there's some credibility to
it?"
>> There could be.
>> Yeah. What is it? 12 scientists or 11
scientists. Four of them were from uh
NASA. Yeah.
>> And I want to say JP is it JPL? The
other four were uh um nuclear fusion
plus weapon and the other three were
guys with secret clearance, not direct
contact with each other. 11 scientists
are dead or missing. It was only a
matter of time before conspiracy
theorists hit the White House.
>> Half-hazard grouping of recent cases
emerged from the one paranormal
investigator described as mystery
mongering data mining. It also made the
ideal fodler father for the president
and our leading media personalities
alike. Okay. So, I don't know if I'm
fully there. Okay. I don't know if I'm
fully there that something's going on,
but one of the guys, his name is uh is
it David Whitlock? Whit Wilcox. Can you
go to the tweet of David Wilcox? I think
>> Oshana sent it to you. If you go into
your text uh uh uh Yeah, he sent it to
you. Oshana sent it to you. If you go to
his text, he sent you um the l the the
tweet he had in 2022
of um tweet he had in Yeah. There you
go. This is in 2022.
>> I plan on living not suicidal at all.
Just concerned about what happens when
you prove God is real. Okay. This is
2022. Three and a half years ago. Go a
little bit lower rap. May God bless your
soul. Such a possible. Now that's April
21st.
Okay. And then you see all the other
stuff that's coming. If he did kill
himself, it was DW murder. So the
market's kind of reacting. What's going
on here? There just a lot of questions.
But tell me what are you thinking? I
think it it bears investigation.
>> Listen, the Israelis have been killing
Iranian scientists for forever. We
probably kill um scientists. Uh other
countries likely kill scientists. I have
no idea if these guys are connected. I
mean, apparently work-wise they're not
connected. But may maybe there's a
foreign actor out there that has a
policy that requires,
you know, a technological setback and
you do that by killing scientists. I
don't know, Rob, what what do you know?
What do you know about the 11
scientists? Because they're saying they
they were working on stuff. They had
certain patents patents. They had
certain things they knew about. You
know, some of it related to the UFO. I
mean, you got to realize this is like a
beautiful, you know, uh, uh, playing
field for guys that want to go into, you
know, maybe there's something there.
Maybe they're doing this. Maybe the
aliens, maybe they're hiding it from us.
But
>> you and I were were joking before we
went on about MC. Well, maybe it wasn't
you. It was one of the guys. We were
talking about MEC. And a lot of the the
requests that I get on MCT are related
to UFOs. And I always say the same
thing. My very first question on my very
first day at the CIA when I met my boss
for the first time for lunch, where are
the UFOs? And he laughed and he said,
"That is the first question that every
one of us has asked." [laughter]
And I'll tell you what I was told. He
said, "That's not what we do here. If
there are any UFOs, all that stuff's at
the Pentagon." Well, we always get a
chuckle out of that. But when I was 17
years old, my mom and dad bought a
restaurant in a neighboring town. We
lived in Newcastle, Pennsylvania. This
restaurant was in Sharon, Pennsylvania.
It's only 15 miles away, but you have to
go through Amish country. Thus, my
dislike of the Amish, so you have to go
through Amish country to get there. And
the Amish don't use electricity, so it's
very, very dark. One night, my dad and
I, it was a Friday night. My dad and I
used to work 11 to 7 on weekends,
midnight shift. So, we're driving to the
restaurant going through Amish country.
We see this brilliant blinding flash of
light, not very high off the ground,
maybe 1500, 1200, 1500 ft. There's a
second flash and a third flash. And we
were both looking up at it and then this
orange
saucer lit up and it's just hovering
there.
>> What year is this?
>> This is 1981.
He pulls over to the side of the road. I
said, 'What in the world is that? We get
out of the car. We're just standing
there staring at this thing. A guy pulls
up behind us. He gets out of his car and
he says, "What is that?" And my dad
said, "I don't know." And then it went
like that at this fantastic speed that
just defied the laws of physics. We get
back in the car. We stood there for a
minute waiting. Is it going to come
back? So, we get in the car. We start
driving again. And I said to my dad, and
mind you, I was a kid. I said, "So,
should we do something? Should we like
call the cops or something?" And my dad
said, "And say what?" We saw a flying
saucer and then it flew away. People are
going to think we've lost our minds. And
so, we only told my mom the next day. We
didn't say anything to anybody. But I
have never forgotten it. In the
meantime, I moved to Washington a year
later. My uncle owned a restaurant in
Oldtown Alexandria, Virginia. His son
was u an F5
pilot or whatever it was, F-16 pilot.
And I mentioned this to him like, "Oh, I
saw the craziest thing last year. I saw
this flying saucer with my dad." And he
said, "Oh, we see those things all the
time." He said, "One time I saw one
shoot up out of the ocean."
And I said, "You kidding me?" He said,
"No." We said, "We fill out these forms.
They're classified. We send them to the
Pentagon." He said, "Every pilot has
seen them." What? This is crazy. This is
crazy. Every pilot has seen them.
>> So, not every person who seems crazy is
crazy.
>> Yeah. I mean, do I do I believe that's
And I wonder 81.
>> Can 81, how advanced were we with drones
in 81? I don't
>> I know, right? Had we even thought of
drones by 81?
>> I don't know. I don't know. When When
were uh when did drones become public,
you know, available to the public? What
year did drones become available to the
public?
>> So that's it. You're talking 81.
>> 20 something years.
>> That's right. Before.
>> So it's not like, you know,
>> and when you went in, you weren't like,
I got to figure this thing out. You
know, I'm going to get into this. Yeah.
I'm going to figure this thing out. I'm
going to go,
>> you know.
>> Did anything anything get close where
you're like, maybe there nothing?
>> Not even vaguely close. What one thing
that I that I did get a kick out of when
I got there, we we didn't have computers
yet. I'm embarrassed to even tell you,
we we had we had IBM Select Electric 3
typewriters at our desks and then we got
these big boxes called Delta Datas with
the little tiny green screen and um
yeah, Delta Data.
>> Go to image.
>> Oh, there it is. Delta computer.
>> Go to images.
>> They had these little green screens.
There they are. There's the Delta data.
So, um, yeah, that's the one. That's
that's the one. Um, and, uh, and so all
the files were paper files that went on
these, they were on these, uh, these
rollers. They went all the way up into
the ceiling and then came back down. The
ceilings were a good, you know, 15, 20
feet, and then they went up into the
ceiling, came down. So, every once in a
while as I'm researching somebody, I
would run across an old professor of
mine
>> from when I was at school at GW.
>> But no,
>> nothing no nothing on UFOs. Not a word.
>> It's funny. I just pulled up the story
on these 11 science. Rob, what did you
pull up? Did you pull up anything on the
scientists? Because what it's telling me
is, okay, 10 or 12 scientists who have
either died or gone missing since 2022.
Many were high security fields. Nuclear
research, aerospace, NASA, FBI,
Department of Energy, NASA, White House
are involved in a coordinated review.
The Congress launched a probe calling it
potential national security really
threat. Some officials have floated
possibilities like foreign intelligence
involvement. China, Russia, Iran
security breaches or just unrelated
incidents being grouped together. A NASA
nuclear engineer, Josh Josh Joshua
Leblanc was found dead after being
reported adding the list and raising
urgency. Important reality check expert
saying no confirmed link between the
cases. Many deaths have been explained
accident suicides illness. The pattern
may partly be internet driven narrative
building.
>> Sure.
>> One of the stories is about a William
Neil Mc uh Castland MC right there. So
that's one of the stories that prompted
everything. If you can just go to the
New York Post story right there, retired
Air Force general, uh, worked on
classified aerospace programs,
disappeared in 2026. So, he's one of the
stories. And the other one is Amy
Escridge. Amy Escridge. There you go.
Right there. Amy Esridge was a
researcher into advanced uh, propulsion,
anti-gravity concepts. And that's the
picture we've seen all over the
internet. Uh, we've seen that she said
definitely did not plan death by
suicide. Friend, go a little bit lower
to read that one. Uh, uh, where do we
have it? There's thought she was a
target. Uh, she thought she was a
target. Research friend from uh,
Escridge believed she was being targeted
for her work in propulsion technology.
Uh, per Melbourne, she claimed she was
being physically and psychologically
attacked and provided pictures uh, to
him of her disclosed discolored hands.
Amy to a friend, if you see any report
that I killed myself, I most definitely
did not. Milbour said Escaridge told him
to believe any reports that she had died
by suicide. Told him not to believe that
she died by su. She turned up dead.
Eskridge died on June 11, 2022 in
Huntsville, Alabama. Her death, but
officially ruled a suicide from a
selfinflicted
inflicted gunshot wound.
>> It's very unusual for women to shoot
themselves.
Yeah, it's normally they shoot their
husbands or they shoot, you know, if it
is it's a it's it's a s situation is the
other way around. Yeah. There's this
thing called the invention secrecy act
of 1951. I don't know if you're familiar
with it or not.
>> Never heard of that one.
>> Yeah. So, the invention secrecy act of
1951 was created by the US government by
this senator from two sides under
Truman. signed it and they they gathered
6,000 patents that the government's had
since which they would pay you off and
you can never make money and never talk
about it.
>> What?
>> And it's something about six. Go a
little bit lower, Rob. The secrecy
orders can bar public disclosure
entirely, prohibit sales to anyone
outside the defense sector, block
exports, and seal restricted
applications as classified. So, if you
go deeper into this, this is something
that John, you would get a kick out of
if you look into this. The Invention
Secrecy Act of 1951. Uh I we were
introduced to this by uh Gear
uh uh Steven Grier rap, if I'm saying it
correctly, he did a documentary on this.
If you've never seen it,
>> it's worth watching. So, this is where
some people speculate that uh you know,
some of these inventions could cure
cancer. some of the inventions would
disrupt the oil industry because cars
could drive based on just water and so
we don't need to do all this other stuff
with oil industry. So, and there's some
credible stories behind how people
disappeared at the time. So, I don't
know is there some credibility to these
stories? Maybe. I definitely would like
to see journalists investigators go a
little bit deeper to see what happened
here with all these people that are
saying I'm not suicidal and then they
disappear. So, who knows? But uh um if
you're watching this and you have any
questions for John Kiryaku, you got to
help him get to the super heavyweight.
He's very close.
>> I know, right?
>> Send him a MC. He's actually very active
and responds uh to folks out there. And
then John's also You got a podcast?
There you do.
>> Yeah. Got a podcast. Uh there's one
that's kind of in flux, but the one I'm
really really proud of is on uh Apple
podcast called John Kuryaku's Deadrop.
And it is, I'm proud to say, in the top
onetenth of 1% of all podcasts.
>> Really?
>> Yeah.
>> Sick.
>> It's taken off.
>> Well, let's put the link below uh on uh
on the podcast. Let's put the link
below. And John, as usual, every time we
talk, I get a kick out of it because
>> you're one you I don't know if you you
obviously know this.
>> You're an incredible storyteller. Oh my
god. You're an incredible storyteller.
It is not a easy. You're you're
extremely curious, interested, you have
your own opinions, which makes it very
entertaining. Thank you.
>> And then at the same time, I can listen
to you for hours because of how good you
are at telling stories. And that's not a
skill a lot of people have. So, I
appreciate you coming out again as usual
and being a class act.
>> And uh I know we got a couple other
things we're talking about. Maybe we'll
do something where the audience can come
to a live event and see you.
>> I I'm in.
>> And that'd be great.
>> I'm in.
>> Yeah. I look forward to that. John,
thank you.
>> Thanks so much.
>> Anytime. Take care everybody. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
>> Hi everybody. I'm John Kuryaku, former
CIA officer. Please find me on Man. We
have a lot to talk about. CIA, FBI, DoD,
torture, secret prisons, international
renditions. Maybe you or your child want
to apply for a job at the CIA and are
looking for some tips. Let me know.
There's a lot we can talk about. You
pick the subject, we'll make it happen.
Again, it's on MCT. Thanks, and I'll see
you soon.